Am I really a child?
本当にぃ　子供かなぁ
本字幕由诸神字幕组出品，仅供学习交流，禁止用于商业用途
更多中日双语字幕，尽在 www.kamigami.org 和微博 @诸神字幕组
日听 Keishin Cc  翻译 domi  Akashi   校对 はばやし  小伍  时间轴 神埼魯蒙  压制 咸鱼
What is that?
なにあれ
Um...
えっと…
This is a tool called a "cell phone."
これは携帯と言って　重要な要件で俺を呼び出す道具で
It's used to call me for important matters.
Your "tool" needs to learn when not to interrupt.
時と場所を選ばないなんて　無粋な道具ぅ
Sir Tarou
From the Minister?
閣下
Greetings, gentlemen.
皆様ぁ　こんな夜半にわざわざ御足労様
Thank you for taking the time to visit so late at night!
Thus, the JSDF Fought There!
to
kk
Thus, the JSDF Fought There!
u
ni
na
Thus, the JSDF Fought There!
特に何も望むことなんてない　身の程は知っているさ
to
ni
I don't really have anything I'm wishing for
mo
no
kk
zo
to
u
mu
kk
ko
ni
to
u
na
n
te
na
i
ni
na
mo
ni
no
mo
zo
no
mu
zo
ko
mu
to
ko
na
to
n
na
te
n
na
te
i
na
mi
no
ho
do
wa
mi
i
sh
I pretty much know my place.
i
t
te
i
no
ru
mi
sa
ho
no
do
ho
wa
do
sh
wa
i
sh
t
i
te
t
i
te
ru
i
sa
ru
so
n
na
bo
ku
so
sa
de
Even so, I think deep down that I don't wanna let anything go
そんな僕でさえも奥の方に
sa
e
om
n
ou
so
o
ku
no
na
ho
n
u
ni
bo
na
ku
bo
de
ku
sa
de
e
sa
om
e
ou
om
o
ou
ku
o
no
ku
ho
no
u
ho
ni
u
yu
zu
ri
ta
ni
It seems I'm only playing "the good girl".
ku
譲りたくない　意向程度はあるらしい
yu
na
i
ii
ko
tte
zu
i
yu
to
ha
a
ru
ra
sh
i
ri
zu
ta
ri
ku
ta
na
ku
i
na
ii
i
ko
ii
tte
ko
i
tte
to
i
ha
to
a
ha
ru
a
ra
ru
sh
ra
i
sh
ma
mo
ru
t
i
Protecting something is harder than I thought,
te
ma
an
ga
i
守るって案外と難しいね
to
mu
mo
zu
ma
ka
sh
i
ru
ne
mo
t
ru
te
t
an
te
ga
an
i
ga
to
i
mu
to
zu
mu
ka
zu
sh
ka
i
sh
ne
i
a
ki
ra
ne
But it's not like that means I'm gonna give up!
me
ru
a
wa
ke
ja
諦めるわけじゃないけど
na
i
ke
ki
do
a
ra
ki
me
ra
ru
me
wa
ru
ke
wa
ja
ke
na
ja
i
na
ke
i
do
ke
ao
i
so
ra
no
ao
ha
At the far reaches of the blue sky - the end of these connected roads,
te
t
su
青い空の果て　繋がった道の行方
na
ga
t
i
ta
ao
mi
chi
no
yu
ku
e
so
i
ra
so
no
ra
ha
no
te
ha
t
te
su
t
na
su
ga
na
t
ga
ta
t
mi
ta
chi
mi
no
chi
yu
no
ku
yu
e
ku
hi
to
wa
e
People still won't come to understand one another... but I'm fine with that
wa
ka
ri
人と人は分かり合えない　だけどいいんじゃない？
a
to
e
hi
na
i
da
ke
do
ii
n
to
ja
na
i
hi
to
wa
ka
ri
a
e
na
i
da
ke
do
ii
n
ja
na
The door I'll open will have everything changing,
i
na
hi
ra
i
ta
to
hi
bi
i
ra
開いた扉は全てを変えてゆく
hi
wa
su
be
te
i
o
ra
ka
e
ta
te
i
yu
ku
to
ta
bi
to
ra
bi
wa
ra
su
wa
be
su
te
be
o
te
ka
o
e
ka
te
e
yu
te
ku
yu
so
re
wa
a
ka
so
ku
t
Just like the break of dawn!
それは暁のように
su
re
ki
so
no
yo
u
ni
wa
re
a
wa
ka
a
t
ka
su
t
ki
su
no
ki
yo
no
u
yo
ni
u
Episode 10  Despair and Hope
What happened? What's going on?
どうした　何が起きてる
The mission is a failure! The mission is a failure!
作戦は失敗　作戦は失敗した
What happened? A Japanese attack?
一体何があったんだ　日本の攻撃か
No!
違う
こ…混乱していて
A-Amidst all the confusion,
we ran into operatives from another country.
ほかの国の連中と　それと
And...
A girl in a kimono...
着物姿の少女
何を言ってる　返事しろ
What are you saying? Come in!
伏すんでろ
Stay down!
Don't move!
動いちゃダメ
Damn it!
クソ　何が起きてるか分からねえ
I've got no idea what's going on!
They're CBP and MSS!
奴らザスローンと国家安全部だぜ
Russian and China are after the same thing we are?
ロシアや中国も　俺たちと同じ狙いだったのか
What do we do?
どうする
化け物め
Monster!
クソ　クソ　クソ　クソ　クソ
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Damn it!
クソ
Damn it...
なんてこった
Oh man...
Group Alpha, signal lost.
グループアルファ　反応消失
No sign of any enemies in the area except for Subject Black.
対象ブラックを除き　周辺の敵勢反応すべて消失
No heat sources.
熱源ありません
That girl's supposed to be a demigod, right?
あの娘　亜神とか言ってたな
W-We have a Case 3.
対処第三項　公安に出動要請を
Requesting help from Public Safety.
What is all this?
な　なにこれ
So many bodies...
こんなにたくさん
すぐに公安が来るはずだが　俺たちもここで待ってるわけにはいかん
Public Safety will be here soon,
but we can't wait here.
Tomita, Kuribayashi, get any weapons you think you can use,
富田　栗林は使えそうな武器を回収して　みんなの荷物をまとめさせろ
and get everybody's stuff together.
了解
Roger.
ピニャ殿下とボーゼスさんも　着替えて出発の準備を
Princess Piña and Bozes-san,
please change and get ready to go.
し　承知した
U-Understood.
No matter how badly it is injured, my body always regenerates.
この体は　どんなに傷を負っても再生する
亜神は死なない
Demigods don't die.
No...
いいえ…
We can't die.
死ねないの
All we've done lately is run.
最近　ずっと逃げてばっかり
全然休暇になってねえな
Some vacation this is.
I'm just glad the Defense Ministry has ownership of that inn.
あの旅館が防衛省共済組合の施設で良かったですよ
Who knows what would've happened if we'd decided to go to a normal inn.
飛び込みで普通の旅館に入ってたら　今頃…
Yeah.
だな
隊長　前方
Captain, forward.
Sorry.
ごめんね
悪いけど　降りてくれるかな
Think you could get out?
Hey, if he's a bad guy, I can shoot him, right?
ねえ　悪人なら撃っていいよね
It'll leave a bad taste in your mouth!
後味悪いって　まだ酔ってるのか
Are you still drunk?
But what do we do?
だけどどうするの
If I try to knock him out like on TV,
殴りつけて気絶とかテレビみたいなことすると　下手すれば死んじゃうよ
that might actually kill him!
そりゃまずいだろう
That would be bad.
伊丹　殺傷せず無力化ができれば良い
Itami, you just need to neutralize him without killing him?
レレイ？
Lelei?
な　まっすぐ銀座に行くのやめよう
Hey, let's not head straight to Ginza.
They might've set up an ambush.
待ち伏せされたらきつい
But we'd be safer beyond the gate than sticking around here.
しかし　変にこっちに居るより　「門」の向こうの方が安全ですよ
We'd be safer in a war zone? Talk about ironic.
戦闘地域の方が安全って皮肉
Lady Piña wants to know
ピニャ殿が訪ねたいと
そもそもなぜ妾は逃げ隠れしなくてはならぬのかと
why we have to run and hide in the first place.
そうですよ　私も思います　なぜですか
That's right! I want to know, too!
Why?
Captain! Tell us, please!
隊長　教えてください
What's going on?
今何が起こってるんですか　隊長
Captain!
Well, you see...
実はな…
俺にもよくわからん
I don't know, either!
なんでやねん
What the heck?
Wait! We can work this out!
待った待った待った
話せばわかる
Quit screwing around, or I'll shoot.
いい加減にしてください　撃ちますよ
おい　まだ酔ってんのか
Hey, are you still drunk?
酔ってません
No!
待たれよ　これから妾の推測を言うので聞いてくれ
Wait.
First, let me state my own hypothesis.
I need to confirm something.
まず確認したい
Have I been sold out?
妾は売り渡されたのではないか
No, that's impossible.
いや　それはありません
一日二日の間に　度重なる乗り物と予定の変更が続いておきた
In the span of a day or two,
we've changed vehicles and destinations several times.
そしてついに　先ほどの旅亭での襲撃　怪しい出来事が多すぎる
And then there was the attack at the inn.
There have been too many disruptions.
We're here to mediate negotiations between a country called Japan and the Empire.
妾たちは二ホンという国と帝国との交渉の仲介　つまり講和のために来た
In other words, we're here for peace talks.
察するに　それを快く思わない勢力と進めたい勢力が有り　せめぎ合っている
I believe there is a faction which desires this
and one which does not, and they're fighting.
Am I wrong?
違うか
Let me get this straight.
つまり君は我々に貴重な政治カードを切らせた上に
Not only did you force us to play an extremely valuable political card,
パラ・ミリチームも全滅
you also lost an entire paramilitary team,
without securing even a single visitor to show for it?
更に　「来賓」の一人も確保できなかったと
The reports say they encountered agents from another country.
報告では　我々以外の国の工作員との遭遇戦があったとされて…
This is not the time for excuses.
今は言い訳の時間ではない
Don't you realize that, Graham?
そうだろう　グラハム
Yes.
はい　必ず「来賓」を確保します　大統領
I promise I'll secure the visitors, Mr. President.
It's warm.
あったかい
You just hit the button, and it comes out!
押しただけで出てくるなんて
How does that work?
どういう仕掛けぇ
分からない
I don't know...
But there was one in the JSDF base at Alnus, too.
けど　アルヌスの自衛隊基地にもあった
A forest fairy, a dark demigod,
森の妖精に漆黒の亜神
そして賢き魔導師か
and a brilliant mage.
Which do you like best?
誰が好み？
I'd guess the elf, based on looks.
耀司の好みからすると　エルフの子
Yeah.
まあな
性格的には黒ゴスの子
Personality-wise, the black goth girl.
Yeah.
ああ
And the platinum blonde makes you want to protect her, maybe?
保護欲がそそられるのは　プラチナブロンドの子かなあ
You sure know me.
大変良くわかってらっしゃる
How many years have we been together?
何年付き合ってると思ってる
Ow!
いて
Welcome back.
おかえり
はい　お待たせ
Here you go.
Oh, thanks!
おお　サンキュー
Sweet Red Bean Soup
With Mochi
おし　おし…　なぜおしるこ
Sweet Red Bean Soup
With Mochi
Why red bean soup?
We chose what looked most delicious.
美味しそうなものを選んできたわ　どう？
How did we do?
間違っちゃいないけど
You're not wrong, but...
I brought you two some, too.
皇女様達も
Thanks.
ああ　すまない
あの　俺の飲み物は？
Um... don't I get any?
何かやったの
What did you do?
Nothing. That's the problem.
何もしなかったんだよ
Today at 2:00 PM,
本日十四時　銀座事件の献花台に
Rory, Tuka, and Lelei are scheduled to visit the Ginza Memorial.
ロゥリイ　テュカ　レレイの三名が献花予定
After that, they're going to go back to the Special Region.
その後　特地への帰途につくらしいっと
The three of them are
visiting Ginza at 2:00 PM.
Really?
Can we see them if we go?
Thanks for the info.
Who are you?
よーし　食いついて来た
Okay, they took the bait!
Okay, let's go!
Is that true?
Were there plans to visit the memorial today?
今日献花なんて予定ありましたっけ
I just asked them.
俺がさっき三人に頼んだんだ
So, Risa, any response?
で　どうだ　梨紗　反応あるか？
There sure was!
ばっちりよ
People loved the video of them at the Diet, after all.
参考人招致の映像がネットで大好評だったし
If this works, we should be able to get a thousand of our "friends,"
うまくいけば
彼女たちを一目見ようとするお友達を千人ぐらいは動員できるはず
who are trying to get a glimpse of them.
サンキュー
Thanks.
With all those people,
そんだけ集まりゃ　さすがの工作員の連中も動きにくいだろうな
it'll be hard for even those agents to attack.
ほかのサイトにも　昼まで同じように書き込んでおくわ
I'll put the same info on other sites by lunchtime.
梨紗がいてくれて助かったよ
I'm so glad you're here, Risa.
もうすぐ朝か
It's almost morning, huh?
It all ends today.
今日で全部終わる
We'll be released from this endless game of hide and seek.
このずっと続く追いかけっこともおさらばだ
Thus, the JSDF Fought There!
Early this morning, the world was shocked when Prime Minister Motoi
本日未明　緊急入院した本位総理大臣
Prime Minister Motoi Emergency Hospital Visit
Motoi Resigns, Enters Hospital
announced his sudden resignation
その突然の辞意表明は
Shock
各界に衝撃をもって受け止められています
after an emergency hospitalization.
The opposition party has denounced his actions as irresponsible.
野党勢力は首相の辞意を「無責任」と批判しています
あ　あの…
U-Um...
What do you think about Prime Minister Motoi's sudden hospitalization
本位総理の突然の入院と辞意表明について　あなたはどう思いますか？
and subsequent resignation?
えっ　辞めたんですか
He quit?
I don't know...
と言っても…
Of course he quit.
辞めて当然じゃない
I'm sorry. I'm not interested.
すみません　興味ないんで
栗林ちゃん　頼むよ　面白いコメント　もらってよ
Kuribayashi-chan, please!
Get us some interesting comments.
すみません
I'm sorry.
I can't hear you!
聞こえない
面白いコメントとは意外性のあるコメントのこと
By interesting comments, I mean surprising comments!
Okay!
はい
わ　私だって　頑張ってるんですよ
I-I'm doing my best, you know!
What?
なんだ
There are a lot more people all of a sudden.
なんか人　増えましたね
Agent                                    Graham
Everyone's ready.
皆　準備はできているようだな
Once they pass the guardhouse, it'll be hard to make a move.
詰め所を越えられたら　手出しは難しい
We need to nab them right here.
なんとかここで「来賓」を回収しなければ
Agents from the other two nations have already been sighted nearby.
他の２国の工作員も　すでに近くで確認されています
This is a difficult mission.
難しい任務だ
We lost our entire team in Hakone,
ハコネでチームは全滅
首相の辞任で我々のカードは帳消しにされてしまった
and our card lost its value when the Prime Minister resigned.
Listen. Our only hope is to
いいか　俺たちに残された方法は
cause a panic when they appear,
奴らが現れたら　パニックを起こし
同時にテレビ局の回線を切断
and simultaneously cut the TV connections.
Then we grab them fast.
そして速やかに「来賓」を回収するしかない
Was there an event scheduled here?
何か行事が予定されていたか
There are too many people.
人の数が異常だ
We're completely stuck.
全然動けません
参ったなぁ　まさかこんなに集まるなんて
Oh, jeez...
I didn't think there'd be so many.
Is this an army that's going to attack the Empire?
もしかして帝国に攻め入る軍勢か？
Where did they all come from?
どこからこれだけの群衆が…
どうします
What do we do?
We'll have to walk,
歩いていくしかないな
but...
けど…
Wouldn't it be dangerous to go outside?
外に出たら　危なくないか
そりゃ　危ないっすよ
Sure would.
But we won't get anywhere at this rate. What do we do?
でもこれ　絶対動きませんよ　どうします？
It's okay.
大丈夫よぉ
Hey, Rory! Wait!
こら　ロゥリィ　待て
Oh, come on.
いいじゃなぁい
Hey, you.
ねぇ　貴方ぁ
Where's Ginza?
ギンザはどっちぃ？
This is bad.
ヤバイな　群衆にどんな人間がいるか分からない
We don't know who's in that crowd.
To the people who lost family in the Ginza incident,
ロゥリィたちは銀座事件の遺族にとっちゃ　初めて見る敵国人だぞ
they're seeing an enemy for the first time.
I don't know about Rory,
ロゥリィはともかく　ピニャさんたちを外に出すわけには…
but we really can't take the Princess out there.
Yeah. Maybe we should give up for today—
今日は止した方が…
But even if we try it tomorrow,
でも　明日にしたとしても　また工作機関が待ち構えていますよ
those agents will still be waiting for us.
I'm sure.
だろうな
ロゥリィ様
Rory-sama!
本物だ
情報は本当だったんだ
Just like on TV!
テレビに映ってた通りだ
I can't believe it!
信じられない
異世界の人だぞ
A girl from another world!
ロゥリィ様　最高
Rory-sama is the best!
If we don't go now, the Prime Minister's resignation
今行かないと　首相の辞任も梨紗の人集めも無駄になるか
and Risa's efforts would have been in vain.
Damn it! It's like we're running from debt collectors.
くっそ　まるで借金取りから逃げてるみたいだ
Risa, sorry, but this is goodbye.
梨紗　悪いが　ここまでだ
Take the car somewhere and abandon it.
車は適当な所まで乗って　放置しといてくれ
ちょちょちょちょっと　先輩
Wait, Senpai!
Thanks.
よろしくな
You know I can't drive!
私ペーパードライバーなの　知ってるでしょう
You can do it!
お前なら大丈夫
意味分かんない
What are you talking about?!
Don't make that face.
そんな顔するなよ
Are you coming back?
また帰ってくる？
Probably not for a while,
しばらくは無理だろうけど　また連絡するよ
but I'll be in touch.
More importantly, pay me back!
それよりも早く借金返せよな
If my doujinshi sells, I'll put it in your account!
同人誌が売れたら　ちゃんと振り込むわよー
Take care.
元気でな
Sergeant Tomita, Sergeant Kuribayashi.
富田二曹　栗林二曹
We are now going to guard our five guests from the Special Region.
これより　特地からの賓客５人の警護につく
If anyone tries to hurt them...
もしも彼女たちを害そうとする者がいれば
Shoot.
撃て
了解
Roger!
レレイ
ありがとう
レレイちゃん
We just got word that the girls from the Special Region,
昨日の国会を賑わした特地の少女たち一行ですが
who appeared at the Diet yesterday, have arrived in Ginza.
先ほど銀座に来ているとの一報が入りました
After laying flowers at the memorial,
they'll be returning to the Special Region.
彼女たちは献花の後　特地に帰るという情報が入っております
Their fans heard the news,
それを聞きつけたファンが駆けつけて
銀座は身動きがとれないほどの人出になっています
and crowded Ginza so much that it's shut down the city.
現地での栗林さーん
We'll go to Kuribayashi-san, at the scene!
A-A...
栗林さーん
Kuribayashi-san!
あ　え　い　う
A-E-I-U—
は　はい　栗林の銀座です
Th-This is Ginza, reporting live from Kuribayashi!
I mean, this is Kuribayashi, reporting live from Ginza!
いや　銀座の栗林です
そちらはどうなっていますか？
What's going on down there?
The three of them are heading towards the memorial
大変な人出の中
お三方が周囲の人に手を振りながら
献花台に向かって　近づいてきています
while waving at the huge crowd gathered here.
Oh!
It's not just the three of them. There are others as well.
お三方だけでなく　他にもおいでのようです
見たところ　８名いらっしゃいます
I see eight in total!
Huh?
あれ
Sis?
お姉ちゃん
Who's there?
誰か
Huh? Nanami?
あれ　菜々美
What are you doing?
あんた　何やってんの？
A-A TV broadcast!
て　テレビの中継
ねぇ　お姉ちゃん　特地からの３人にインタビューできない？
Hey, sis!
Can I interview the girls from the Special Region?
無理無理　献花が済んだら　すぐ特地に帰らないと
No way.
After the flowers, we're going back to the Special Region.
You're going back?
また行くの？
Yeah.
そうだ　菜々美　私も一つお願いが…
Oh, Nanami! I have a request...
やっほー　お母さん　元気してる？
Hey, Mom! How you doin'?
I won't be home for a while,
しばらく家に帰れないけど　休み取れたら必ず帰るからね
Hey! What is this? What about the interview?
おい　なんだこれ　インタビューは？
but as soon as I can take a vacation I'll be heading home.
ごめんなさい
I'm so sorry!
But there've been people after us the past two days.
でも　一昨日からずっと狙われてて
Thanks to this country and that country,
trains were stopped and hotels set on fire.
どっかとどっかとどっかの国から　電車は止められ　ホテルは放火
They might be after us right now!
今ここでも狙われてるかもねぇ
お姉ちゃん
Sis!
What? Is there a problem?
なに　何かまずいの？
There sure is!
まずいよ
This is bad.
厄介だな
Oh, Graham-san.
やあ　グラハムさん
何の用だ　駒門
What do you want, Komakado?
ハコネの件は話がついたはずだろう
The Hakone matter was settled.
Oh, your assault on the inn?
旅館の庭に乱入した件ですか
そちらさんの仕事については　文句を言うなと言われておりますが
I've been told not to complain about your mission,
but I do need to keep an eye on what the other countries are up to.
他の国はさすがにマークしなくてはいけないものでね
By the way, Graham-san.
ところで　グラハムさん
ＣＩＡの局員と他の国の工作員って　どうやって見分けたらいいんですか？
How am I supposed to tell the difference between CIA agents
and agents from other countries?
何だと
What?
If I can't tell the difference, I'm liable to make mistakes.
他の国の工作員と区別つかないと　見間違えちゃうんですよ
You can't mean—
まさか…
If you're concerned, then make a phone call.
心配なら　電話してみればいい
There's just no way to tell, you know.
いやあ　区別がつけられないもんでねぇ
You—
お前っ
Itami, I've gotten them off your back.
伊丹　露払いはしておいたぜ
What?
何だと
ＣＩＡチームが全員押さえられた？
The entire CIA team has been arrested?
申し訳ありません
I'm sorry.
それに何だ　あの女自衛官は
And what's with that JSDF girl?
カメラの前で　あんなことをペラペタと
Talking about all that on camera...
モトイめぇ
Curse that Motoi!
Not bad.
やるじゃないか
Give the order to withdraw.
撤収の指示を出せ
A bell must be rung to lay all of the dead to rest, yeah?
たくさんの死者のために　鎮魂の鐘が必要ね
Someone sound a bell.
誰かぁ　鐘を鳴らしてちょうだい
A bell?
鐘？
Thank you.
ありがとぉ
レレイ
ロゥリィ
テュカ
Captain! We're here to get you.
隊長　お迎えに上がりました
Huh?
って　あれ
疲れた
So tired...
Hey. Did you enjoy your vacation?
よう　休暇は楽しめたか？
You call that a vacation?!
全然休暇になってねぇ　年末に三日取り直すからな
I'd better get three more days off at the end of the year!
If you want that, you'll have to go negotiate...
ま　そうしたければ　交渉することだ　直接陸将に
...directly with the general.
It was such a fun trip!
面白い旅だったわぁ
Very interesting! I want to go back!
興味深い　また行きたい
Shopping sure was fun!
買い物　楽しかったわね
What is this?
何じゃ　これは
It shines!
光った　光ったぞ　レレイ
It shines, Lelei!
I'm back!
ただいまー
Huh?
あれ
お父さん
Dad?
もう　目を離すと　すぐこれなんだから
Jeez, take my eyes off him for a second and this happens.
The other side of the gate was overwhelming.
門の向こうは圧倒的であった
If we continue this war,
このまま戦争を続けたら　帝国は間違いなく負ける
the Empire is certain to lose.
No, it will be destroyed.
いや　滅亡するだろ
Your Highness...
殿下
We'll leave for the capital at dawn.
明朝には　ここを出立して帝都に向かう
We must prepare for peace talks as soon as possible.
講和の準備をせねば　一刻も早く
I will...
妾は
...put an end to this war.
この戦争を終わらせる
unmei niwa sakaraenai ne deatteshimatta
I guess I just can't fight my fate - we've already met!
運命には逆らえないね　出会ってしまった
何があるか分からないけれど　キミと出かけよう
nani ga aru ka wakaranai keredo
I don't know what might happen,
kimi to dekakeyou
but I'm heading out with you!
心おどる遠い景色は　なんだか違って
kokoro odoru tooi keshiki wa
There's something a bit different
nandaka chigatte
about the far off scenery,
doa o akete itsumo no choushi sa
But once we open the door, we're back to
ドアを開けて　いつもの調子さ　どうぞよろしく！
douzo yoroshiku
our usual pace, so let's keep on together!
mada kimerarenai sanpo koosu
We still can't decide which course to walk
まだ決められない散歩コース
いろんなものが多すぎて
iron na mono ga oosugite
There are just too many things to consider.
光のうずに吸い込まれて　まだ迷ってるの？
hikari no uzu ni suikomarete
Pulled into a whirlpool of light,
mada mayotteru no
We're still undecided!
走り抜けたあの瞬間は　甘い甘い香りの中で
hashirinuketa ano shunkan wa
Amidst a sweet, sweet scent,
amai amai kaori no naka de
We can feel a new future within this place.
新たな未来　ここに感じてる
arata na mirai koko ni kanjiteru
Upon a song, disappearing high into the sky,
tondekieru uta ni noseta
But the moment we manage to run on through
飛んで消える歌にのせた　空へ空へきれいな星に
sora e sora e kirei na hoshi ni
I'll cast a spell that sparkle brightly,
キラキラ光るように　魔法かけようから
kirakira hikaru you ni mahou kakeru kara
I'll cast magic which shines bright
Episode 11  Visitors
次回　「ゲート」
Next time on GATE:
"Visitors."
来訪者